Contact

36,vrundawan nagar, near nandanwan ,nagpur hasanbagh police chowki 9284359273 (Mobile) shubhkotal@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/shubhamkotal (LinkedIn) github.com/shubhamkotal (Other)

Top Skills

Data Analysis
Python (Programming Language)
Data Science

Certifications

Technical Analysis
Supply chain Analytics
Financial Market
Fundamental Analysis
Demand Analytics

Honors-Awards

#1 Runner up in Hackathon #3 Place in The National Level Project/Poster Competition

#1 place in HACKATHON

Shubham Kotal

Data Scientist

Hyderabad

Summary

I am trained in Machine Learning, Artificial Intelligence, Neural Networks, Deep Learning, and Big Data Analytics modules. I also specialize in tools like Python, R, Tableau, Hadoop, Pyspark, and SQL. I aim to use this knowledge for doing predictive, descriptive and prescriptive analysis which in turn will provide insight into business operations and help it grow.

Mb - 9284359273

Experience

Soulpage IT Solutions
Data Scientist
May 2019 - Present (1 year 4 months)
Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Data Scientist at SoulpageIt Solutions.

TeacherOn.com
Data Science Trainer
December 2018 - Present (1 year 9 months)
One on One live Data Science classes

UrbanPro.com
Data Science Trainer
May 2019 - Present (1 year 4 months)
Giving one on one live Data Science Classes

Quantopian Inc.
Community Member
January 2020 - Present (8 months)

Independent
Trader
February 2020 - Present (7 months)
Page 1 of 2

Independently trading in the Indian market

Education

International School of Engineering (INSOFE)
PGP in Big Data Analytics and Optimization , Information
Technology · (2018 - 2019)

Yashwantrao Chavan College of Engineering
Bachelor of Engineering in Electrical, Electrical and Electronics
Engineering · (2014 - 2018)